RESUME - KATIE LOCK

Location: Ascot Vale, VIC 3032

Email: hello@katieelsomlock.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/katielock92

ABOUT ME:

Emerging web developer, currently completing a software development bootcamp at Coder Academy and seeking a junior developer role for 2024. 10 years prior professional experience in business operations roles across various industries. Building a reputation for being adaptable, efficient and willing to get the job done. Passionate about contributing to grassroots sports in my spare time.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY:

- ► October 2019 Present: **People Operations Specialist** at mx51 Previous titles: Business Operations Coordinator, Assistant Accountant
 - Key operational specialist in a fast-growing fintech startup
 - Have recently transitioned into a full HR-focused position, having previously assisting across the finance, people, operations and risk teams
 - Highlights to date include providing key administrative support on Series A capital raise, implementing an ATS for recruitment and uplifting internal security reporting to ensure audit success
- ▶ October 2017 October 2019: **Finance and Operations Manager** at SA1NT
 - Led the finance and customer service functions for an eCommerce startup
 - Introduced a variety of business process improvements while performing a broad and highly demanding role
- ▶ November 2016 October 2017: **Cloud Integration Specialist** at Pitcher Partners
 - In-house specialist in cloud accounting software and business apps
 - Conducted a number of software implementation projects across a vast variety of clients in addition to work with ongoing bookkeeping clients
- ▶ September 2012 November 2016: **Senior Customer Experience Specialist** at Xero
 - Provided world-class customer support for accounting software, while consistently having some of the highest KPIs in a global team
 - Trained and mentored new employees

2007 - 2012: Multiple retail roles

VOLUNTARY EXPERIENCE:

- ▶ November 2022 Present: **Director** of Australian Flying Disc Federation
- ▶ January July 2022: **Team Manager** for Pie Wagon World Ultimate Club Championships
- ▶ June 2021 August 2022: **Canteen** Committee at West Brunswick Amatuer Football Club
- ▶ April 2017 August 2019: **Treasurer** and **Board Member** of Heads of State Ultimate
- ► November 2018 July 2019: **Team Manager** at Ultimate Australia Team Australia for the Asia-Oceanic Beach Ultimate Championships
- ▶ November 2017 April 2019: **Board Member** of Ultimate Victoria
- ► August November 2017: **Team Manager** at Ultimate Victoria Victorian Mixed Team for the Australian Under-22 Ultimate Championships
- ▶ 2017 Present: **Commentator** at World Flying Disc Federation and Ultimate Australia

EDUCATION:

2023

Coder Academy:

▶ **Diploma of IT** (Software Development Bootcamp)

2020-2021

Accredited Online Training:

▶ Diploma in Human Resources

2011-2013

Victoria University of Wellington:

▶ Bachelor of Commerce (Accounting)

2009-2010

Wellington Institute of Technology:

▶ Diploma in Business